(liquid bubbling)
Don't you poke around inside me.
Not without my permission!
I hate that, punk ass!
Then you come down here
and I'll tear you open!
(opening theme music)
"Episode 6: After Rain"
You're being awfully
hostile, aren't you?
Ha!
You got that right!
You expect kindness
after you murdered me?
So that's the thanks I get
for healing your arm and hand?
Let's not forget
that right after that
you ripped out my heart!
Where are we
anyway, is this hell?
I'm not crazy about being
stuck with you for eternity.
But I'll make it work.
And you'll pay!
(charge yell)
I hope you're ready for this!
He was aiming for where I stood?
You fell for it!
Got you!
What the?
You're just so predictable.
Ah!
I was sure I'd landed
that one perfectly!
Damn it.
This isn't the afterlife.
This place is my Innate Domain.
Innate Domain?
Fushiguro talked about!
Or think of it as
being in my mind.
In short, you could say
we're not dead just yet.
Oh.
If you'll accept my conditions,
I'll fix your heart and
bring us both back to life.
Cocky bastard.
Don't act like you're
doing me a favor!
I know you don't
want to die either!
But the situation has changed.
Very soon I'll be able to
see something interesting.
I have just two conditions.
Number one is whenever
I chant the word Extension,
you'll surrender your
body to me for one minute.
Two, you'll completely
forget you made this promise.
No way!
I don't know what
you're really after here
but it's shady as hell.
I finally get what
you're really about now.
You are pure evil!
And I'm not lending
you my body ever again!
During that minute I
won't kill or injure anyone.
Is that enough to
address your concerns?
Loser.
[Yuuji] Like I'd
ever believe you!
It's not about whether
you believe me or not.
This is a pact, a geas.
I'll be the one
punished if I break it.
(pain scream)
And if you pursue selfish
gain beyond your means,
you will suffer retribution.
I'm certain you've
experienced that for yourself.
It wasn't a problem before!
Hm.
Huh?
Oh, you mean that time
I wanted to switch, too.
And you were just doing
what that sorcerer told you to.
A pact founded
in mutual interest.
That's one of the key
factors behind all jujutsu.
Fine, then.
Get off of me already.
I'll accept your conditions.
I don't understand
exactly what you're up to,
just that it means
I'll come back to life!
I'd never accept that!
Bring me back to life
without any conditions.
It's all thanks to you I
died in the first place.
Well how about this then?
We'll fight to the death
and I'll do it without
conditions if you defeat me.
But if I win then you live
only under my two conditions.
Yeah!
I'll kick your ass for...
[Gojou] You know, I have
a deeply flawed personality.
[Ijichi] I know.
Ijichi, expect a forehead flick.
(gasp)
A forehead flick?
Being a teacher is not my style.
Do you know why I
decided to become
a teacher at this
school in the first place?
Ask me.
Why did you do it?
Because I have a dream.
[Ijichi] You have a dream?
Yup.
As you can see in
this case with Yuuji,
the top of the jujutsu
world is a den of vice.
Conservative fools,
traditional fools, arrogant fools,
just plain fools.
It's a bargain sale
on rotten mikan!
And I want to reset that
garbage jujutsu world.
Murdering all the fools at
the top would be an easy task.
But no fix, 'cause they'd
all just get replaced
and there'd be no revolution.
Plus if I did that, no one
would want to follow me.
That's why I chose
education instead.
As a way to raise up
strong, clever compatriots.
And sometimes it's also
why I send students
to do my missions.
It's tough love.
Or a chance for
you to slack off.
And they're all talented.
Especially Hakari,
the third-year,
and the second-year, Okkotsu.
They'll become jujutsu
sorcerers on a par with me.
Yuuji would have been
one of them as well.
Hey you two.
-Hm?
I'm going to get started.
Are you gonna watch from there?
(shock gasp)
Hm?
Whoa!
Where're my clothes?!
G-G-G-Gojou!
He's alive!
Are you seeing this?
-He's alive!
-Ijichi stop.
I'm a little bummed.
Yeah, well.
It's embarrassing
but, who are you?
[Gojou] Hi, Yuuji!
Huh?
Welcome back!
Yo!
Well thanks.
What a pain.
I'm going to have to
revise all the reports.
No, leave them as-is.
I want us to give Yuuji the time
to regain the minimum power
before he gets targeted again.
And so, I need you
to just leave him listed
as deceased on the records.
Ah.
So, you're gonna keep
Itadori hidden away?
No.
I'll have him back in time
for the Exchange Event.
[Shouko] Why?
The reason is simple.
No one can be allowed
to take the events of youth
away from the young
people they're designed for.
I bet this'll shock em!
Not anyone.
I've gotta get outta
here, right now!
I've always had a strong
sense of responsibility,
and I've been saving all my pay
so I can send my four
younger sisters to college, too!
But even I can't fight
my survival instinct!
And I know if I go
near that table, I'll die!
[Jougo] Satoru Gojou!
I wonder, could we kill
him if we joined forces?
No, he'd either flutter
out of your grasp
or, in the worst case,
you'd all get exorcised.
I would recommend you pour
your energy into sealing him
rather than killing him.
How?
Do you have a lead?
We'll use the special-grade
cursed object Prison Realm.
Prison Realm?
Table five hasn't
ordered anything.
I'll go and hurry him up.
He's taking up a whole table.
I'm sorry boss, but I quit!
Huh?
Hey, you come back here!
Prison Realm?
That horrible thing?
It's warm.
The AC quit working?
Relax, Jougo, or you'll
overheat the place.
How are you, sir?
Have you decided on...
Aagh!
(terror scream)
I wish you wouldn't cause
such a commotion, Jougo.
Oh this is nothing.
(horror scream)
What?
(coughs)
Glad we didn't
choose finer dining.
(panicking)
Tell me, Getou.
How strong am I in
terms of Sukuna's fingers?
[Getou] As a
conservative estimate?
I'd say eight or nine fingers.
Yeah?
That's plenty!
Give me the Prison Realm!
I'll add it to my collection!
And in return I'll promise you,
I'll kill Gojou.
Help!
(melodious electronic music)
(upbeat electronic music)
By the time we
arrived on the scene,
your son was already dead.
I'm sorry.
To be honest,
I was skeptical about saving
any of the people in there.
However, my
friend was different.
He wasn't successful,
but after we confirmed
your son's death
you know he's tried to
bring his body back for you.
It's okay.
"Okazaki Tadashi"
(sigh)
Please take this.
I know it's not much.
I'm sorry we weren't
able to save Tadashi.
It's all right
Don't apologize.
I'm the only one
who will mourn him!
No one else will even care.
(sobbing)
(intense running efforts)
Yo, you're late, Megumi.
Kelp.
Where have you been?
And what does it matter to you?
Answer me something.
Hm?
As a sorcerer, what kind of
people do you want to save?
Huh?
What difference
should it make to me
whether my actions
save anyone at all?
I knew I shouldn't
have asked you.
Say what?
Fushiguro!
Quit asking interview
prep questions
and come switch places with me!
I am so totally sick of
these school uniforms!
Let me go buy some cute
tracksuits for this event!
And here we go.
(yelling)
What the hell are they doing?
Falling practice.
Mustard leaf.
You're both pretty
weak in close quarters.
So first.
See if you can
land a blow on us.
Do that and we'll talk.
You're already a
head above the rest
when it comes to
close combat, Yuuji.
So what you need
to learn to do next is
control cursed energy.
And we need to add to your
basic knowledge of jujutsu.
"Smile"
What's wrong?
Sorry.
I'm just happy 'cause
I know you're the best
and you're the one I
wanted to have train me.
Before, I was too weak
and I couldn't save anybody.
Worse, I nearly
got Fushiguro killed.
I won't be able to face
them the way I am now.
Make me strong.
Make me into the strongest!
(chuckles)
You've got a keen eye.
Well actually, you already
told me you were the strongest.
All right, well
first take a look
at those two soda
cans over there.
Whoa!
[Gojou] This is
with cursed energy,
and that's cursed technique.
I see.
No I don't.
Uhh, okay.
Then think of cursed
energy as electricity,
and cursed technique
as electrical appliances.
Electricity by itself
is hard to use, right?
That's why we run that
electricity through appliances
to achieve various results.
Here, I just fired off
pure cursed energy.
Whereas here, I
channeled cursed energy
into a cursed
technique to activate it,
twisting the can with jujutsu.
Alright!
So I get to learn a really good
cursed technique now huh?
[Gojou] No.
You can't use cursed techniques.
Huh?
Aside from simple Shikigami
and your basic barriers,
cursed techniques
are fundamentally
etched into your body
from the day you're born.
Huh?
So the power of
a jujutsu sorcerer
is about 80% innate talent.
(dazed)
You okay?
Yeah.
I just thought I'd be able
to pull off thunder or fire
or a power bomb or something.
You can do a power
bomb just like Ohnita.
Aww!
This sucks big time!
I wanted to pull off a
Spirit Gun or a Bankai
or a Rasengan or a Dodon Ray!
-What a drag!
-You just can't use them yet!
But eventually, Sukuna's
cursed techniques
will be engraved into your body!
I wanted to fire
off a Kamehameha!
Let's just ignore the
things you can't do
and work on enhancing
your strengths.
We will imbue your fighting
style with cursed energy!
I'm way more scared of
someone with solid basics
than I am of inferior jujutsu.
Like I said your
talent for close combat
is already top-notch.
(sudden realization gasp)
But wait a sec!
I already know how to do that!
Get up.
Against that special-grade,
I got it to work, somehow.
Then give it a try.
Hit me here.
Not that I think you can.
Don't blame me if you get hurt.
Come one, hurry up, try it.
That punch had
zero cursed energy.
But why?
Cause it requires
negative emotions.
In the fight that
you're recalling,
you were probably brimming
with fear and with anger.
Ah!
So you have to
constantly be flipping out
in order to use
your cursed energy?
But now that you mention it
Fushiguro's always ticked off.
Demon Dogs!
(barks)
Not quite.
What's wrong?
I'm irritated all of a sudden.
-Huh?
-No, I don't mean with you.
-[Toge] Salmon roe.
-Only a month and a half left.
So no daydreaming!
Now here, try your
hand at the long one next.
This actually feels pretty good.
All students are trained
to produce cursed energy
using even the faintest
sparks of emotion.
And they're trained in ways
to avoid wasting
their cursed energy
when their emotions
are flaring up as well.
(dismayed gasp)
There are several
training methods for this.
The one I'm going to use on
you is especially exhausting.
Okay, what's that?
Watching movies!
Watching movies?
Yup!
From classics to
C-grade horror movies
to terrible French movies.
Nonstop as long as
you can stay awake.
Of course you won't be
watching them all alone.
(snoring)
You'll be watching
them with this guy.
[Yuuji] What's with the
cute-but-creepy doll?
It's cute?
It's another cursed corpse.
From the Principal!
Yeah, I recognize his style.
But, I'm not seeing
the point here.
Don't be hasty, now.
You'll see soon enough.
That cursed corpse will wake up
and attack you just like that,
if you don't keep cursed
energy flowing into it.
Like I said before,
we've got all kinds of
movies here to choose from.
Tear-jerkers,
thrillers, comedies.
Movies to make you laugh
or cry or gross you out.
Your first assignment
is to watch an movie
from start to finish, without
waking the cursed corpse.
This trains you to maintain a
steady output of cursed energy
no matter what
emotions you feel.
You can't use too
much or too little.
(aggravated flailing)
(relieved sigh)
For now I have it set to the
faint level of cursed energy
that you're able to produce.
But soon it'll start
demanding greater output,
so you can't let
your guard down.
I couldn't let it down
even if I wanted to.
Where do you want to start?
I recommend this one.
The heroine's annoying but
she dies gloriously in the end.
Thanks for the spoiler.
Hey, I know!
Let's start with an action ad...
Oh, come on!
Hey!
Keep that cursed energy steady!
Carrying cursed tools, huh?
I'm fine with supplementing
close combat with weapons,
but with my cursed technique
I want to be able to
have my hands free.
Swords cost you time
sheathing and unsheathing them.
So Zenin, you often carry around
two or even more
around with you don't you?
How do you do that?
Oh I make Panda carry them.
I knew I shouldn't
have asked, part two.
Some jujutsu sorcerers
keep cursed spirits
that can store and
retrieve objects.
Yeah, but he can't do
that, it's a rare ability.
And it takes time
to tame them, too.
But if you do find
any, let me know.
[Panda] It'll cost you a
year's supply of Calpas.
But there's just,
one thing I don't get.
Why did you run?
Kind of a waste of your talents.
Do I have the potential
to beat special-grades?
Is that what he meant by that?
Tuna, tuna.
Huh?
What's that?
Zen'in?
I think I know how to do it.
Ura-Hara?
Where's Ura-Hara?
Am I lost?
Do I cut the red
wire or the blue one?
I need to know!
In the area where I used to live
we had designated trash bags.
What are you talking about?
We're running out of time!
And the bags
were red for plastic
and blue for combustible trash.
I thought, shouldn't
it be the opposite?
It should be red!
Anyone would go with red!
Alright, I'll trust you.
(anxious breathing)
Ugh!
(boxing bell ringing)
(coughs)
Don't attack me while
I'm drinking soda!
Don't drink.
But you can't watch a
movie without chips and soda!
You have a point there.
Well, Gojou's got to get going.
So just keep hanging in there.
Is this really gonna
make me stronger?
(chuckles)
Oh, yeah.
While you were dead,
did you talk to Sukuna?
Not sure.
And before he
repaired your heart,
did he suggest any
deals or make conditions?
Ohh!
I think he did say
something like that.
But I can't remember
what it was.
I see.
We have some time
before your appointment
with the principal.
Do you want to stop anywhere?
No thanks.
I'll surprise him and
show up early for a change.
Stop here.
[Ijichi] Huh?
Right here?
You go on ahead.
[Ijichi] Agh!
Is this a test or something?
You're going to hit me
if I drive away without
you, aren't you?
Just what type of
guy do you think I am?
[Ijichi] Okay then.
All right.
(banshee attack wail)
(menacing laugh)
I see.
Who are you then?
("Lost in Paradise"
by ALI feat. AKLO)
[s] Juju Stroll!
[] It's Satoru
Gojou's Go Go Gojou!
We are here at my alma mater,
Tokyo Metropolitan
Jujutsu Tech High School.
Oh no!
A boy in trouble already?
He's a new student, having
trouble producing cursed energy!
Let's try to help him!
Imagine yourself on a
narrow pathway at school.
Standing before you
is a row of college boys,
and you can see they
haven't noticed you.
You want to kill them all!
And so you--
Shut up.
(tense music)
"Episode 7: Assault"